Hello LinkedIn team,
My name is Cristian, and today I’m presenting MetricMind.
MetricMind is a web intelligence platform designed to help users analyze
and activate digital presence signals through authorized platform connections.
Users can access the platform either by creating their own credentials
or by signing in with Google.
In this demonstration,
I will continue using Google authentication.
Once inside, the user can start by entering any website they want to analyze,
which allows MetricMind to identify publicly available digital signals associated with that domain.
At this stage, we see the main analysis panel.
Initially, the platform highlights available integrations, such as Meta,
which will be used in future steps.
After entering a website, MetricMind performs a web intelligence scan
to detect the brand’s digital presence.
This includes identifying publicly available signals such as social media profiles
associated with the website.
The goal is to provide users with a structured view of their digital footprint,
and prepare the environment for authorized connections.
Once relevant signals are identified, the user can proceed to connect their accounts,
including LinkedIn, through secure authorization.
At this point, the LinkedIn connection option becomes available.
The user is then redirected to LinkedIn to sign in and authorize the application
through OAuth.
This ensures that all interactions with LinkedIn are fully compliant
and based on explicit user consent.
After authorization is completed, MetricMind securely receives the necessary permissions
to access basic profile data and enable further actions within the platform.
Once connected, we can see the initial results based on LinkedIn data.
The platform activates signal detection and enables interaction features
such as content publishing.
At this moment, organization-level access is still restricted,
which is precisely why we are applying for the Community Management API.
This approval will allow us to expand these capabilities
to organization pages.
Now, we proceed to create a post directly from MetricMind.
The content is published through the LinkedIn integration,
and once the post is live, we copy its URL.
This URL is then used in the tracking section,
where MetricMind begins monitoring engagement signals.
The platform tracks interactions such as comments and activity related to the post,
providing a structured view of engagement.
All data shown here is obtained through authorized interactions
and user-provided inputs.
Finally, this demonstrates how MetricMind connects web intelligence
with social platform activation in a compliant and user-driven way.
Thank you for your time,
and we look forward to your approval.